(this["webpackJsonpquiz-app-starter"]=this["webpackJsonpquiz-app-starter"]||[]).push([[0],[,function(e){e.exports=JSON.parse('[{"questionText":"What is NOT rewarded for completing the Path of Pain?","answerOptions":[{"answerText":"Special dialogue","isCorrect":true},{"answerText":"A special cutscene","isCorrect":false},{"answerText":"A Hunter\'s Journal entry","isCorrect":false}],"gameSource":"Hollow Knight","reason":"You get a small cutscene between the Pure Vessel and the Pale King, and the Seal of Binding entry."},{"questionText":"Before official release, Scout\'s Stock Primary Weapon was planned to be a Nail Gun.","answerOptions":[{"answerText":"True","isCorrect":true},{"answerText":"False","isCorrect":false}],"gameSource":"Team Fortress 2","reason":"You can see this in the early trailer for the Orange Box!"},{"questionText":"By the National Pok\xe9dex, what Pok\xe9mon is #001?","answerOptions":[{"answerText":"Pikachu","isCorrect":false},{"answerText":"Bulbasaur","isCorrect":true},{"answerText":"Squirtle","isCorrect":false},{"answerText":"Charmander","isCorrect":false}],"gameSource":"Pok\xe9mon","reason":"Bulbasaur is Pok\xe9mon #1."},{"questionText":"What boss does Bowler joke about removing from a Rainbow Run?","answerOptions":[{"answerText":"Gatling Gull","isCorrect":false},{"answerText":"High Priest","isCorrect":false},{"answerText":"Wallmonger","isCorrect":false},{"answerText":"Ammoconda","isCorrect":true}],"gameSource":"Enter the Gungeon","reason":"It is a joke from the developers because of how much players hate Ammoconda."},{"questionText":"Master Mode changes boss patterns.","answerOptions":[{"answerText":"True","isCorrect":false},{"answerText":"False","isCorrect":true}],"gameSource":"Terraria","reason":"Only Expert Mode does this!"},{"questionText":"Who is the first character to speak?","answerOptions":[{"answerText":"Vi","isCorrect":false},{"answerText":"Maki","isCorrect":false},{"answerText":"Kabbu","isCorrect":true},{"answerText":"Eetl","isCorrect":false}],"gameSource":"Bug Fables","reason":"The order goes Kabbu->Maki->Vi->Eetl, if you were curious."},{"questionText":"Based on your choices, how many different bosses can end up being the final boss?","answerOptions":[{"answerText":"2","isCorrect":false},{"answerText":"3","isCorrect":true},{"answerText":"4","isCorrect":false}],"gameSource":"Bloodborne","reason":"It can be, Mergo\'s Wet Nurse, Gehrman, or Moon Presence. They each give a unique ending!"},{"questionText":"As of Repentance, how many bosses can give an ending?","answerOptions":[{"answerText":"9","isCorrect":false},{"answerText":"10","isCorrect":false},{"answerText":"12","isCorrect":true},{"answerText":"13","isCorrect":true}],"gameSource":"The Binding of Isaac","reason":"Both 12 and 13 are accepted, as some may consider Ultra Greed and Ultra Greedier as the same boss for an ending."},{"questionText":"How many Knights are in the Order of No Quarter?","answerOptions":[{"answerText":"6","isCorrect":false},{"answerText":"7","isCorrect":false},{"answerText":"8","isCorrect":true},{"answerText":"9","isCorrect":false}],"gameSource":"Shovel Knight","reason":"Black Knight is not in the group, if you counted him."},{"questionText":"Which of these elements was not present in Borderlands 2?","answerOptions":[{"answerText":"Corrosion","isCorrect":false},{"answerText":"Cryo","isCorrect":true},{"answerText":"Slag","isCorrect":false},{"answerText":"Explosive","isCorrect":false}],"gameSource":"Borderlands","reason":"Cryo was introduced in the next game, The Pre-Sequel."}]')},,,,function(e,t,a){e.exports=a(11)},,,,,function(e,t,a){},function(e,t,a){"use strict";a.r(t);var r=a(0),s=a.n(r),n=a(4),o=a.n(n),i=(a(10),a(2)),c=a(1);function l(){var e=Object(r.useState)(0),t=Object(i.a)(e,2),a=t[0],n=t[1],o=Object(r.useState)(!1),l=Object(i.a)(o,2),u=l[0],m=l[1],w=Object(r.useState)(0),h=Object(i.a)(w,2),f=h[0],T=h[1],x=Object(r.useState)(!0),d=Object(i.a)(x,2),g=d[0],p=d[1];return s.a.createElement("div",{className:"app"},g?s.a.createElement("div",{className:"main-menu"},s.a.createElement("h1",{className:"title-text"},"Riyara's Video Game Trivia"),s.a.createElement("h2",{className:"subtitle-text"},"CISC275 F2021"),s.a.createElement("button",{className:"start-button",onClick:function(){p(!1)}},s.a.createElement("strong",null,"Start"))):null,u?s.a.createElement("div",{className:"score-section"},"You scored ",f," out of ",c.length,function(e){return e===c.length}(f)?s.a.createElement("div",{className:"congratulations"},"A perfect score! Great job!"):s.a.createElement("div",{className:"good-try"},"Thanks for playing!")):s.a.createElement(s.a.Fragment,null,g?null:s.a.createElement(s.a.Fragment,null,s.a.createElement("div",{className:"question-section"},s.a.createElement("div",{className:"question-count"},s.a.createElement("span",null,"Question ",a+1),"/",c.length,s.a.createElement("h3",null,"Game: ",c[a].gameSource)),s.a.createElement("div",{className:"question-text"},c[a].questionText)),s.a.createElement("div",{className:"answer-section"},c[a].answerOptions.map((function(e,t){return s.a.createElement("button",{onClick:function(){return function(e){e?(alert("Correct! "+c[a].reason),T(f+1)):alert("Incorrect! "+c[a].reason);var t=a+1;t<c.length?n(t):m(!0)}(e.isCorrect)}},e.answerText)}))))))}o.a.render(s.a.createElement(s.a.StrictMode,null,s.a.createElement(l,null)),document.getElementById("root"))}],[[5,1,2]]]);
//# sourceMappingURL=main.2d775c2c.chunk.js.map